A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art AAA.neimlero
Archives of American Art
Gone with the Wind perfume - 3.1: Gone with the Wind perfume promotion 1989
Hager hinges - 4.1: 1988
Hanes Hosiery - 2.1: 1980
Merrill Chase - 2.1: 1978
Miller Brewing Company - 4.1: 1984
Nabisco - 2.1: 1988
Ocean Club, Atlantic City - 3.1: Ocean Club, Atlantic City 1982-1990
Olin Corporation, Olin Skier, 1976 - 4.1: 1976 and ov.
PuzzleStix - 3.1: PuzzleStix product idea 1999
Royal Doulton - 3.1: Royal Doulton collectible plates 1974-78, 4.1: 1977, 1981, 1986, 2000
Saks Fifth Avenue - see Saks Fifth Avenue
Sharp Color Copier - 3.1: Sharp copier promotion 1986
skis - 2.2: Joe Hideo Morita 1988-90
Skoal chewing tobacco - 3.1: Skoal Pinch Hitter 1985-1987
Sports Commemorative Satinwood whiskey decanters - 3.1: Sports Commemorative Whiskey Decanter 1979
The Toy Store - see exhibitions
Tropicana Hotel and Casino - see casinos
watches - 2.1: 1986, 3.1: Classic Moments LeRoy Neiman Watch Collection 1989, 3.1: Universal Geneve Timepieces Promotion 1995
Wheaties - see Wheaties
publications - Series 3.2
publicists - 2.2: Barry Landau 1994-96, 2.2: Sterling/Winters Company 1983-84
Puck, Wolfgang - 2.1: 1999
Puerto Rico - 2.1: 1979, 1981, 1984, 1985
Pump Room Bar, 1957 - see bars
Punchinello, 1971 lithograph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 3.1: Royal Doulton collectible plates 1974-78, 4.1: 1973, 1974
Purdue University - 4.1: 1986
puzzles - see promotions, product and service, and collectibles
Q
Quarry, Jerry - see boxing
Quayle, Lynn - 1.1: Lynn Quayle, IIID: Datebooks, 4.1: 1988
Queen Elizabeth of England - 4.1: 1959
The Queen Elizabeth II - 3.1: Queen Elizabeth II Cruise, 1999
R
race car - see auto racing
Race to Erase MS - 2.1: 1993, 1994, 1995, 2000, 2001, 4.1: 2001
>radio - 4.1: 1974, 1985, see also American Federation of Television and Radio Artists
King, Larry - see King, Larry
Stern, Howard - 3.1: Howard Stern, 1994
WNBC Radio - 3.1: WNBC Traffic Helicopter 1981
WPRO Radio Providence, RI - 2.1: 1990
Rangers Hockey Magazine - 4.1: 1967
Raphael, James
James Raphael, 1987 - 4.1: 1987
Rattiner, Dan - see Dan's Papers
Rawlings Gold Glove Award - 4.1: 1992
Reagan, President Ronald and Nancy - 2.1: 1981, 1988, 3.1: Nolan Ryan, 1981, 3.1: U.S. Savings Bonds Campaign 1987-88
Ronald Reagan, 1988 - 4.1: 1988
real estate - 2.1: 1986
recipe - see Heartland Celebrity Cookbook
Red Square - see Moscow
Redgrave, Vanessa - 4.1: 1994
Regatta of the Gondoliers - 2.1: 1984
Regis & Ann Show - 4.1: 1984
Reiner, Rob - 1.1: Friars
representations of LeRoy Neiman by other artists - 4.1: 1989
restaurants and bars
Al Schacht's Restaurant - 4.1: 1967, 1968 and ov
Alexis Tangier, San Francisco - 4.1: 1958
The Bistro Garden - 3.1: Bowles/Sorokko Galleries Exhibition, Beverly Hills 1987, 4.1: undated
Bruxelles Restaurant - 4.1: 1950s
The Buena Vista Café, San Francisco, 1986 - 3.1: 3.1: Nob Hill, Buena Vista and Bowles Hopkins Gallery 1986, 4.1: 1987
Le Café Chambord - 4.2: Playboy 1959, see Appendix E
Café de Flore, Paris, 1964 - 4.1: 1996
Le Café Lautrec, 1963 - 4.1: 1963
Café de la Paix - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Related Exhibitions
California Cuisine (The Lark Creek Inn), 198? - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 4.1: 2004
Central Park Boathouse - 3.1: Central Park Boathouse Painting 2002-2003
Chumley's - 4.1: 1968
Le Cirque - 3.1: Circus, 2000, 4.1: 2004
Corona Café, Chicago - 4.1: 2001
Duke's Fish & Grill - 4.1: 1985
Ernie's, San Francisco - 4.1: 1958, 4.2: Playboy 1961, see Appendix E
F.X. McRory's Whiskey Bar, Seattle, 1979 - 3.1: F.X. McRory's Whiskey Bar 1979-80, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992 and 1993-2002, 4.1: 1995
Fouquet's - 2.1: 1993
Fouquet's - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Related Exhibitions, 4.1: 1996
Fouquet's, 1977 drawing - 4.1: 1996
Gallagher's Steak House, New York - 3.1: Gallagher's Steak House - The Neiman Collection 2002
Le Grand Vefour - 2.1: 1993
Harry's at Hanover Square - 4.1: 1985
Harry's Bar, 1985 - 4.1: 1995
Harry's Wall Street Bar - 4.1: 2002, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992
Iron Horse Restaurant - 4.1: undated
Jak-Nicholas Restaurant - 4.1: 1973
Lark Creek Inn - see California Cuisine
Left Bank Café
London House, Chicago - 4.1: undated
Maxim's de Paris - 4.1: 1963, 4.2: Playboy 1961, see Appendix E
McSorley's Irish Pub, New York - 4.1: 1980
Mister Kelly's - 4.1: undated
The Mixologist, 1959 - 4.1: 1999
Moose's Restaurant, San Francisco - 4.1: 2003, 2004, 2005
Morton's of Chicago - 3.1: Morton's of Chicago 1982-present, 3.2.12, 4.1: 1997, 1998, 2000
Neil De Vaughn's - 4.1: 1987
Neiman's Restaurant and Lounge, Carlsbad, CA - 3.1: Neiman's Restaurant and Lounge 1980s, VII: Neiman's Restaurant, Carlsbad, CA, 1980s
Nello - 4.1: 1999
P.J. Clarke's, New York, 1978 - 3.1: Elayne Galleries Solo Exhibition and P.J. Clarkes, Minneapolis, 1978, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992, 4.1: 1978, 1989, 1995
Peppy's Pomme Soufflee - 4.1: 1973
Pierro's on the Park - 4.1: 1994
Polo Bar, Westbury Hotel - 2.1: 1978
Polo Lounge - see Polo Lounge, 1988
Pump Room - 4.1: 1974, 4.2: Playboy 1958, see Appendix E, see also The Ambassadors Hotel
Pump Room Bar, 1957 - 3.2: LeRoy Neiman Art and Lifestyle 1974, 4.1: 1950s
Rao's - 2.1: 2002
Frank at Rao's, 2005 serigraph of earlier painting - 4.1: 2005
Restaurant Antoine - 4.1: undated
Romanoff's - 4.2: Playboy 1959, see Appendix E
Rosati's, Via Venito - 4.2: Playboy 1968, see Appendix E
Rush Street Bar - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992
Sardi's, World Billiard Championship - 4.2: Playboy 1963, see Appendix E
Shelly's New York - 3.1: Shelly's New York Restaurant 2000
Spago, Los Angeles - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
The Stag's Head Bar, Dublin, 1961 - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992
Tavern on the Green - 4.1: 1991, 1998
Tavern on the Green, 1990 painting and 1991 serigraph - 2.1: 1990, 1991, 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 4.1: 1991, V: 1991
Carriage at Tavern on the Green, 1997 drawing - 4.1: 1997
Toots Shor Bar - 2.1: 1988, 1.2: Knoedler: Serigraph Release Ads
Tratoria del'Arte - 4.1: 1991
'21' Club - 3.1: Dress the Jockeys at '21' Club, New York, 2001
Bar at 21 - 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries, 4.1: undated
'21' Club (exterior), 1990 - 3.1: '21' Club 1990
Two Bar Men, 1965 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992
The Wimbledon - 4.1: 1975
retail prices, list of prints, 1986 - 2.1: 1986
retail stores - see Neiman-Marcus
Revelli, Cynthia - see Licensing Art and Design by Cynthia Revelli
Revlon - 2.1: 1992
Rhino Records - 4.1: 1991
Rhythm & Smoke - see cigars
Rice, Jerry - 4.1: 1995
Riggins, John, John Riggins - 4.1: 1972
Riker, Lyn - V: 1980s
The Ring Magazine - see boxing
Ringside Madison Square Garden, 1964-65 - see boxing - Introduction of the Champions of the Ring, 1964-65
Rivalry, 1975 - see college sports: football: Ohio State Buckeyes
Rivera, Chita - 4.1: 1995
Rizzuto, Phil, The Scooter, 1994 - 3.1: Phil Rizzuto 1994
The Robb Report Magazine - see automobiles
Robinson, Jackie - 3.1: Jackie Robinson, 1997
Jackie Robinson, 1993 - see Jackie Robinson Foundation
Jackie Robinson, 1997 - 3.1: Jackie Robinson, 1997
Jackie Robinson Sliding Home, 1997 - 3.1: Jackie Robinson, 1997
Jackie Robinson Foundation - 3.1: Jackie Robinson Foundation 1993
Robinson, Patrick - 2.1: 1977
Robinson, Sugar Ray - see boxing
Robinson's, Los Angeles - 4.1: undated
Rock for the Cure - 4.1: 2004
Rocky films - 3.1: Rocky films 1980-90
Rocky - 3.1: Advertising Layouts 1980s
rodeo - 4.1: 1977, 2000
Rogers, Kenny - 4.1: 1999
Kenny Rogers, 1982 watercolor - 3.1: Childrens Diabetes Foundation Carousel Ball
Rolling Stone Press - 4.1: 1982
Rolls Royce - see automobiles
Ronald McDonald House - 2.1: 1999, 4.1: 1998, 2000, 2001, 2003
Rooney, Art, Art Rooney, 1972 - 2.1: 1977, 4.1: 1972
Roosevelt University, Chicago - 1.1: Education and Teaching, Miscellaneous, undated
"Rooster," 1981 film - see film
Roques, Karin Adrian v. - 2.1: 1997, 1999
Rose, Donna - 2.2: Donna Rose and Art Brokerage Inc. Correspondence
Rosen, Leonard - 2.1: 1980, 1981, 1982, 1983, 1984, 1987
Rosenbaum Galleries - see exhibitions
Rote, Jr., Kyle - 3.1: Rotonda Superstars 1973-75
Rotonda Superstars - 3.1: Rotonda Superstars 1973-75
Royal Doulton - 3.1: Royal Doulton collectible plates 1974-78, 4.1: 1977, 1981, 1986, 2000
Royce Carlton, Inc. - 2.1: 1978
Royer, Victor - 2.1: 1984, 1986
Rudy, Jeanette Cantrell - 2.1: 1994, 1996, 1998, 4.1: 1994, Jeanette Rudy, 1994 - 2.1: 1994, 4.1: 1996
running - see also track and field
Ashford, Evelyn - 4.1: 1987
Barron, Gayle - 2.1: 1983, 1984
Boston Marathon, Boston Marathon, 1979 - 4.1: 1981, 1990
Coghlan, Eamonn, Eamonn Coghlan Winning the 1985 Wanamaker Mile, 1985 - 3.1: Millrose Games 1986-1995
Dixon, Rod - 4.1: 1998
New York City Marathon - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
Classic Marathon Finish, 1985 serigraph - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
Fred, This Run's For You, 1990 - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
New York City Marathon, 1987 - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
Runner's World Magazine - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
Shorter, Frank - 2.1: 1973
The Year of the Runner TV series, LeRoy Neiman host - see television
Rush, Rick - 4.1: 1999
Rush Street Bar - see bars
Russell, Bill - 4.1: 1968
Ruth, Babe - 4.1: 1973, 1995
Ryan, Nolan
Nolan Ryan, 1981 - 3.1: Nolan Ryan, 1981, 4.1: 1991
S
Sadat, Anwar - 3.1: Peace Treaty, 1980
safari - see LeRoy Neiman On Safari
sailing - 4.1: 1950s, 1964, 1985, 1994, America II, 1986 - 3.1: America II, 1986, 4.1: 1986
America's Cup - 4.2: Playboy 1966, see Appendix E
America's Cup, 1964 - 3.1: Advertising Layouts 1980s, 4.1: undated 1970s, 1978
America's Cup, Australia, 1987 - 2.1: 1986, 4.1: 1986, 1987
America's Cup Stars and Stripes, 1987 - 2.1: 1987
Boat Club, 1956 - 4.1: 1950s
Boats and Boats, 1960 oil on board - 2.1: 1978
Girallia Yacht Race - 4.2: Playboy 1965, see Appendix E
Harbor Boat House, 1955 - 4.1: 1950s
Hawaiian Sailing - 3.1: Advertising Layouts 1980s, 4.1: 1984
High Seas Sailing - 4.1: 1999
High Seas Sailing II, 1998 - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999
Men, Boats, and the Sea, 1955 - 3.1: Art Institute of Chicago Instructors Exhibition 1955
Sail Boats, 1953 - 4.1: 1998
Sailing - 4.1: 1985
Swell Sailing - 4.1: 1983
Turnberry Isle Yacht Club - 3.1: Turnberry Isle Yacht and Racquet Club Exhibitions 1982-83
Yawl Sailing, 2001 - 4.1: 2001
St. Bonaventure University - 1.1: Honorary Degrees: St. Bonaventure University 1999
St. Clare's Hopital and Health Center - 4.1: 1995
St. Francis College, Brooklyn Heights, New York - 1.1: Honorary Degrees (ov), 3.1: Brooklyn Bridge, 1995
St. John's University - 1.1: Honorary Degrees, 2.1: 1978, 4.1: 1985
St. Paul, Minnesota, bicentennial painting, Baghdad of the Midwest, 1975-76 - 3.1: St. Paul Bicentennial Painting, Baghdad of the Midwest, 1975-76
St. Paul Area Chamber of Commerce - 2.1: 1976
St. Paul Museum - 4.1: 1997
Winter Carnival painting, Ice Palace, 1985 - 3.1: Ice Palace 1985-86
St. Tropez - 4.2: Playboy 1964, see Appendix E
St. Tropez, 1995 - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue Catalog 1994-1999
Saks Fifth Avenue - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue Catalog 1994-1999, 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Correspondence
View from Saks, 1995 - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999
Saleski, Don - 4.1: 1974
Salon d'Automne - see exhibitions, group: Grand Palais
Saltman, Sheldon - 2.1: 1976
Salvation Army - 2.1: 1999
San Diego Zoo - 2.1: 1977
San Francisco, CA
Bay Area Baseball, 1990 - 3.1: Bay Area Baseball debut at Bowles/Sorokko, San Francisco 1990
City by the Bay, 1993 - 3.1: San Francisco Series 1991-93
San Francisco by Day, 1991 - 3.1: San Francisco Series 1991-93
San Francisco by Night, 1991 - 3.1: San Francisco Series 1991-93
Washington Square (Moose's), 2002 - 4.1: 2003
Sandburg, Carl - V: Playboy 1961-63
Sandusky, Joe, Joe Sandusky - 4.1: undated 1990s
Santa Claus - 4.1: 1992
Sapir, Judge Eddie - 2.1: 1978, 1979, 1983, 1988
Satchmo - see Armstrong, Louis
Satinwood Whiskey - see promotions and collectibles
Saugatuck - see Ox-Bow
Saviano, Rudy - 2.1: 1999
savings bonds - see U.S. Savings Bonds
Sayers, Gale - see I Am Third, by Gale Sayers
Scaffidi, Phil - 2.1: 1981
Scarpa, William and Cathy - 2.2: William and Cathy Scarpa 1991-99
Schaefer Brewing Company - 2.1: 1976, 1979, 1980, 1981, 4.1: 1976
Schoenfield, Ed - 4.1: 1986
Schmeling, Max - 4.1: 1989
Schmidt, Michael - 2.1: 1980
The Slugger, 1979 - 2.1: 1980, 4.1: 1990, 1999
Schulberg, Budd, Budd Schulberg, 1970 drawing - 4.1: 2004
Schulz, Axel - 4.1: 1995
Schultz, Charles - 2.2: Playboy Enterprises Inc. 1970s
Schultz, Dave (hockey player) - 4.1: 1974
Schultz, Dave (wrestler) - see wrestling
Schumsky, Felicie - V: 1970s, see also Felicie, Inc.
Screiber, Al - 4.1: 1994
Schwarzenegger, Arnold - 2.1: 1990, 3.1: LongTerm Projects: American Sportscasters Association Hall of Fame Awards Dinners, 4.1: 1977, 1981, Arnold Schwarzenegger, 1977-78, 4.1: 1977, 1985, 2005
The Scooter, 1994 - see Rizzuto, Phil
Scott Foresman & Company Publishers - 2.1: 1985
Screen Actors Guild - 1.1: Name Tags and ID Cards, 3.1: Rocky films 1980-1990, see also American Federation of Television and Radio Artists
sculpture
Horse Racing Suite, 1977 - 3.1: Sculpture 1977-1987, 4.1: 1978
Defiant, 1987 - 2.2: JoAnn Perse Gallery 1984 -98, 3.1: Sculpture 1977-1987 Seaver, Tom
The Franchise, 1992 - 4.1: 1992, 2001
Segal, Erich - 2.1: 1973
Sehorn, Jason - 4.1: 1999
Seitz, Nick - see golf: Golf Digest Magazine
Self Portrait (at easel) - 4.1: 2000
Self Portrait (close up with cigar and pen), 1997 - 4.1: 1998
Serline, Ollie (LeRoy's aunt) - 1.1: Family (Neiman Studio Archive only), 2.1: 1970s, 4.1: 1972
Sharp color copier - 4.1: 1986
The Sharper Image - 4.1: 1997
Shavers, Earnie - see boxing
Shaw, Robert - 2.1: 1977, 1978
Shelly's New York - 3.1: Shelly's New York 2000
Shenker, Morris A. - 2.1: 1982, 4.1: 1982
Sher Galleries - 4.1: 1987
Sherman, Nettie - 4.1: 1981
Sherry -Lehmann - 2.1: 1997, 1998, 4.1: 1997 and ov
ship - see The Jennifer
shoes - VII
Shore, Dinah - 3.1: Dinah! (Dinah Shore television show) 1974-77
Shorter, Frank - see running
The Shot Heard 'Round the World, 1991 - 3.1: The Shot Heard 'Round the World, 1991
Showboats International - 3.1: Monaco Trip 1994
Shula, Don - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-73
Siegfried & Roy - 2.1: 1998, V: 1999
Sigmond, Aaron - 2.1: 1994, 1995, 1997, 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Selection Cigars 1997
Silverstein, Shel - 2.1: 1973
Silverwood Products - 2.1: 1992
Simon Weisenthal Center - 3.1: Jackie Robinson, 1997
Simpson, O.J. - 4.1: undated 1990s, see football: Cross-Town Rivalry 1967, 1993, O.J. Simpson - 4.1: 1972, 1974
Sinatra, Frank - 1.1: New York Friars Club, 2.2: Sinatra Family Correspondence, 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1967, 3.1: Frank Sinatra Film Drawings Exhibition, Gallery of Modern Art 1967, 3.1: Leo Durocher 1974-94, 3.1: Frank Sinatra Portraits for Duets and Duets II Albums 1993-1995, 3.1: Hofstra Univ. Frank Sinatra Conference and Exhibition 1998, 3.1: Frank Sinatra Classic Duets Album Cover 2002, 4.1: 1979, 1983, 1989, 1998, see also golf, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1960s
Frank at Rao's, 2005 serigraph - 4.1: 2005
Frank Sinatra, 1993 - 3.1: Frank Sinatra Duets and Duets II Album Covers 1993-1995
Frank Sinatra at Carnegie Hall, 1974 - 3.1: Frank Sinatra at Carnegie Hall Poster 1974
Frank Sinatra as the Detective, 1967 - 3.1: Frank Sinatra Film Drawings Exhibition, Gallery of Modern Art 1967
Frank Sinatra at Madison Square Garden, 1974 drawing for poster - 4.1: 1974
Frank Sinatra at Royal Albert Hall, 1989 - 3.1: Frank Sinatra at Royal Albert Hall 1989
Singleton, Isaiah - 2.1: 1996
Singleton, Skip - see tennis: Intelligent Doubles and Intelligent Tennis
skating - see figure skating
skiing - 4.1: 1983, 1995, see also Olympics: skiing
Lady Skier - 4.1: 1998
Little Skier - 4.1: 1974
The Skier, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Skiing, etchings - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972
Slalom, serigraph - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1973
Squaw Valley - 4.2: Playboy 1961, V: 1960s, see Appendix E
Vail Race to Erase MS painting, 1994 - 4.1: 1995
Skoal Pinch Hitter of the Year Award - 3.1: Skoal Pinch Hitter 1985-1987
Slatkin, Leonard, Leonard Slatkin, 1980? - 4.1: 1980
Sliding Home - see baseball
slot machine - 4.2: Playboy - Femlin Paraphernalia
The Slugger, 1979 - see Schmidt, Michael
Smith, Charley - 1.1: Military Service
Smith, Emmitt
Emmitt Smith, 1994 - 4.1: 1994
Smith, Liz - 3.1: Doodle for Hunger I, II, III, IV, V, 2000-2004
Smith Jones, Nancy - 2.1: 1978, 1979
Smithsonian Institution, The Smithsonian Associate Magazine - 3.1: Piazza San Marco, 1990, 2001-2002
Smothers, Tom and Dick (The Smothers Brothers) - 1.1: New York Friars Club
Snead, Sam - see golf - Frost, David
Snyder, Jimmy "the Greek" - 2.1: 1974, 1991, Jimmy the Greek - 4.1: 1982
soccer - 2.1: 1984, 1985, 4.1: 1977, 1979, 1994
AMF soccer equipment - see promotions
Anheuser Busch World Cup poster, 1990 - 3.1: Anheuser Busch World Cup Soccer poster 1990
Chinaglia, Georgio - 3.1: Cosmos soccer 1977, 4.1: 1979, 1998
Cosmos - 3.1: Cosmos soccer 1977
Fairfax Police Youth Club Tournament poster, 1988 - 3.1: Fairfax Police Youth Club Soccer Tournament Poster 1988
Maradona, Diego - 2.1: 1980, Maradona, 1982 - 3.2. Winners, Harry N. Abrams, 1983, Magazines and Catalogs
Pele - 3.1: Economic Opportunity Atlanta 1968 ov., 3.1: Tampa Bay Rowdies soccer 1975, 3.1: Cosmos soccer 1977, 4.1: 1988
The Black Pearl, 1975 drawing - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975-76
Pele, 1975 - 3.1: Tokyo Exhibition 1988
Pele, watercolor - 2.1: 1983
Soccer, 1989 etching - 4.1: 1990
Tampa Bay Rowdies: Soccer is a Kick in the Grass, 1975 - 3.1: Tampa Bay Rowdies soccer 1975
socialites - 3.1: Notes on Hamptons high society 1972
Society of Illustrators of Los Angeles - 1.1: Awards: Citations
soft paintings - 3.1: Soft Paintings 1989, 3.1: Steiner & Young Galleries Exhibition 1989
Solange - 4.1: 1973
Soltner, Chef Andre - 3.1: March of Dimes' Gourmet Gala 1985
Sony - 2.1: 1978, 4.1: 1977
The Sopranos - 4.1: 1999
Sosa, Merqui - 4.1: 1996
Sosa, Sammy, Sammy Sosa, 1999 - 3.1: Good Tidings Foundation 1998-99
Sorenson, Jacki - see dance
Sorokko, Serge - see exhibitions: Bowles/Sorokko Galleries
Sotheby's - see Carousel of Hope, 4.1: 1986, 4.2: Playboy 1972, see Appendix E
souvenirs - see promotions
space shuttle - see Columbia Space Shuttle
Spago - 4.1: 1999
speaking engagements - 4.1: 1977, 1978, 1979, 1980, 1984, 1988
Special Olympics -3.1: Special Olympics Nagano Japan 2005, 4.1: 1986, 1996, Mississippi Special Olympics - 2.1: 1977
The Spectrum, Philadelphia, PA - 2.1: 1991, 1996, 3.1: Philadelphia Spectrum Painting 1991, 4.1: 1992, V: Photographs
Spectrum Fine Art, New York - 3.1: "Ball, Bat, and Glove", Spectrum Fine Art, 1977, 4.1: 1978
Spelling, Aaron - 2.1: 1985
Spinks, Leon - see boxing
Spinks, Michael - see boxing
Spirit Foundation - 2.1: 1999
Spitz, Mark - see swimming and diving
The Sporting Life - 4.1: undated
The Sporting News - 3.1: Iona College Trustee Awards Dinner Dances 1984-95
sports - listed alphabetically by name of sport (i.e. "baseball," "soccer"), with teams listed under heading of appropriate; in some cases college and professional sports are indexed separately. Also search for names of specific athletes.
sports arenas - see Madison Square Garden, Philadelphia Spectrum
sports cards - see trading cards
Sports Collectors Digest - 4.1: 1997
Sports Commemorative Decanters - see promotions and collectibles
sportscasters - see also Cosell, Howard, and Rooney, Art
American Sportscasters Association - 1.1: Awards
Sportsman's Ball - 3.1: Sportsman's Ball 1978
Sportsman's Park, Chicago - 3.1: Sportsman's Park Mural, Chicago 1976
SportsWise Magazine - 2.1: 1980
Springfield Art Association, Illinois - 2.1: 1990
Stadium Tennis, 1981 - see tennis
The Stag's Head Bar, Dublin, 1961 - see bars
Stallone, Sylvester - see Rocky, 4.1: 1987
stamps - 4.1: 1974
"Health in Sports" stamps, 1988 - 3.1: United Nations "Health in Sports" Stamps 1988
"Sport and the Environment" stamps, 1996 - 3.1: United Nations "Sport and the Environment" Stamps 1996
"Superbowl History" Stamps, 1988 - 3.1: U.S. Postal Service Superbowl Stamps 1988
Standard Oil - 4.1: 1974
Stanford University - 3.1: Bill Walsh, 1993
Stanley, Dr. M. Lee - 4.1: undated 1990s, 1996
Stargell, Willie, Willie Stargell, 1980 - 2.1: 1988, 3.1: Willie Stargell 1980, 4.1: 1973, 1987, 1988
Statue of Liberty, Lady Liberty, 1985 - 2.1: 1985, 3.1: Lady Liberty, 1985, 4.1: 1992 Staub, Rusty - 2.2: Manufacturers Hanover
Rusty Staub's Le Grand Orange wine label - 3.1: Rusty Staub 1975-1994, 4.1: 2001 Staubach, Roger - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-73, 3.1: Wheaties 1997, 4.1: 1972, 1973, 1982
Roger Staubach, 1982 - 2.1: 1989, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1997-2002, 4.1: 1982
Stengel, Casey, Casey Stengel, 1993 - 3.1: Casey Stengel 1996, 4.1: 2001
Sterling, Donald - 2.1: 1997, 1998
Sterling/Winters Company - 2.2: Sterling/Winters Company 1983-84
Stern, Howard - see radio
Stiller, Jerry - 1.1: Friars
Sting Like a Bee by Jose Torres and Bert Sugar - see boxing
Stock Market
American Stock Exchange, 1986 serigraph - 4.1: 1986
New York Stock Exchange, serigraph - 2.1: 1996, 3.1: Winter Olympics Lake Placid, 1980, 4.1: 1974
Stock Exchange, silk tapestry - 4.1: 1990
Stock Exchange, London - 4.1: 1983
Stock Market, 1976 serigraph - 2.1: 1977, 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1976
Stop Cancer - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
Stop or My Mom Will Shoot, 1992 film - 2.1: 1991
Strahan, Michael - 4.1: 2002
Strasberg, Lee - 2.1: 1983
Strawberry, Darryl - 4.1: 1990, 2001
Stroh Brewing Company - 2.1: 1988
Stud Poker - see casinos
Studio 54 - 4.1: 1984
Styria Galleries - 4.1: 1988
Sugar, Bert - 2.1: 1972, 1977, 3.1: '21' Club, 1990 (photo), 4.1: 1999, see also boxing: Sting Like a Bee
Summer in Saugatuck, 1960 painting - 2.1: 1987
The Summer School of Painting - see Ox-Bow
sumo - 3.1: Hawaii and Japan 1974
Superbowl - see NFL football
Superstars - see Rotonda Superstars
Supreme Court of the State of New York - 2.1: 1980, 2.2: Judge Frank Affronti 1990 -1999
Supreme Court of the United States - 2.1: 1992
Surfing - 4.2: Playboy 1967, see Appendix E
The Surfer, 1980 - 4.1: 1980 ov
surgery - see The Open Heart, 1982
Swahn Fine Arts - 4.1: 1989, 1991
Sweden - 3.1: Sweden Exhibitions 1976-77
swimming and diving - 4.1: 1987, 3.1: Los Angeles Olympics
Chandler, Jennifer - 4.1: 1987
International Swimming Hall of Fame Museum - 4.1: 1988, 1989
Louganis, Greg - 3.2.9, 4.1: 1987
Olympic Swimmer - 4.1: 1986
Spitz, Mark - 2.1: 1986, 3.1: Munich Olympics 1972, Mark Spitz, 1972 - 3.1: Munich Olympics 1972, 4.1: 1973, 1987
United States Swimming Long Course Championships - 4.1: 1982
Switzerland - 2.1: 1985, 1989
Swoboda, Ron - 2.1: 2002
Symphantasy - see music
T
Takamiyama, Jesse - 3.1: Hawaii and Japan 1974
James Talcott, Inc. - 3.1: James Talcott, Inc. 1975
tapestry - 3.1: Edward Fields, Inc, Carpet Tapestries 1977
Taschen Publishers - 3.1: GOAT (Greatest of All Time - A Tribute to Muhammad Ali) Book by Taschen, 2004
Tavern on the Green - see restaurants
Taxicab Chronicles - 3.1: Taxicab Chronicles 1999, 4.1: 1999
Taylor, Elizabeth - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
Taylor, Lawrence - 4.1: 1996
television - 2.1: 1970, 1978, 4.1: 1972, 1974, 1975, 1977, 1979, 1980, 1985, 1994, 1995, 3.1: Call of the Wild 1993, see also ABC, CBS, American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, The Lone Ranger
ABC Sports - 2.2: ABC Sports
Ampex Video Art - 3.1: Superbowl XII, 1978, 4.1: 1980
Arlene Herson Show - 4.1: 1989
The Black Stallion television show - 2.1: 1990
CBS Sports - 2.2: CBS Sports, 3.1: Superbowl XII, 1978
Channel 13 - 2.1: 1976
Cityscope - 4.1: 1989
Dinah! (Dinah Shore) - 3.1: Dinah! (Dinah Shore television show) 1974-1977
KCTA -TV St. Paul - 2.1: 1976
Larry King - see King, Larry
Kup's Show (Irv Kupcinet) - 4.1: 1972, 1982